A Guide to Paul Bowles: A Bibliography, 1976-1984
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Paul Bowles: A Bibliography 1976-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10501-d
This collection contains 2,958 items.
Jeffrey Miller
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the library by Jeffrey Miller of Belvedere, California on March 26, 1986.
Scope and Content
This collection contains notes and material pertaining to Jeffrey Miller's Paul Bowles: A Bibliography.
Contents List
- Manuscripts
  - Paul Bowles: A Bibliography by Jeffrey Miller 1983, TMs, 516 pages
  - Paul Bowles: A Bibliography by Jeffrey Miller 1984, Page Proofs, ca. 516 pages
  - Index to Paul Bowles: A Bibliography by Jeffrey Miller n.d., Typed cards, ca. 1700 cards
- Miscellaneous
  - Preliminary Material for Paul Bowles: A Bibliography[ca. 1982], Notes, 50 items
  - Notes for the chapter "Books and Pamphlets by Paul Bowles" in Paul Bowles: A Bibliography[ca. 1982], Notes, 203 items
  - Notes for the chapter "Books and Pamphlets with Contributions by Paul Bowles" in Paul Bowles: A Bibliography[ca. 1982], Notes, 114 items
  - Notes for the chapter "Contributions to Periodicals" in Paul Bowles: A Bibliography[ca. 1981-1982], Notes, 194 items
  - Notes for the chapter "Translations" in Paul Bowles: A Bibliography[ca. 1982], Notes, 76 items
  - Notes for the chapter "Unpublished Music" in Paul Bowles: A Bibliography[ca. 1982], Notes, 208 items
  - Notes for the chapter "Recordings" in Paul Bowles: A Bibliography[ca. 1982], Notes, 162 items
  - Notes for the chapter "Miscellanea" in Paul Bowles: A Bibliography [ca. 1982], Notes, 49 items
- Photographs of dust jackets of books by Paul Bowles [ca. 1984], Black & white photographs, 200 items